http://www.wit.edu/support-wentworth/alumni-and-donor-privacy-policy

Alumni and Donor Privacy Policy | Wentworth
Skip to main content
Learn about the campus re-entry process for the Fall 2020 Semester
AcademicsColumn 1Program Finder
Full-Time Undergraduate MajorsMaster's Degree ProgramsPart-Time DegreesWorkforce TrainingOnline Programs
Privacy and Security
Wentworth Institute of Technology is grateful for the financial support it receives from its alumni and donors and understands the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information. The Institute takes alumni/donors’ right to privacy very seriously and recognizes that, to merit alumni/donors’ continued trust, it is important to be transparent and accountable in preserving the confidentiality of the personal information that Wentworth collects and maintains.
General Purpose and Access Restriction
Within the Institute, access to alumni/donor information is limited to Institutional staff members with a legitimate business purpose and need to know, and, as appropriate, those in academic units and programs who support development and alumni relations activities. Academic unit and program leaders’ access to alumni/donor information is restricted to limited alumni/donor information.
Wentworth Institute of Technology will share contact information with third-party vendors for the explicit and limited purposes of facilitating the university’s mission or alumni benefit through development and engagement programs. When such contact information is shared with the third-party vendor, the vendor will first be required to sign a written agreement pledging that the information will be used only for its intended purpose; will be stored securely; and will not be resold or provided to any other individual, entity or organization without the university’s express written approval.
Persons with responsibility for records containing personal information will exercise due care to ensure accuracy, completeness, and data security. Strict physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards will be utilized to protect personal information against accidental or intentional misuse or improper disclosure within or outside Wentworth.
Wentworth Institute of Technology shall continually monitor these practices and procedures to ensure compliance with the principles set forth in this policy. If at some point in the future there is a change to the information usage practices that affect alumni/donor personal information, it will be reflected in the alumni/donor privacy policy posted on this site.
Donor Recognition
Donor contributions may be publicized in donor recognition vehicles produced by the university or other entities, including print, spoken, broadcast and/or web-based media. If donors do not wish their names to appear in these publications, they may notify the Institute’s Advancement Services Office at (617) 989.4547.
Make A Gift Now
Upcoming Events
Friday October 9, 2020Chronic Chats
Tuesday October 13, 2020Faculty Webinar: Session 1 Learn to Navigate Brightspace
Tuesday October 13, 2020Faculty Webinar: Session 2 Communicate & Engage in Brightspace
Tuesday October 13, 2020Faculty Workshop: Voice Thread Basics 2 - Groups and Secure Sharing
Tuesday October 13, 2020Facts and Snacks - How to Make a Happier You
